Finding Aid for Catalogs of Michigan-based automobile companies, 1896-1971 and undated
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Catalogs of Michigan-based automobile companies 1896-1971 undated
Bentley Historical Library (collector)
EA 134 A939 C357
Trade catalogs, brochures and other promotional material produced by Michigan automobile manufacturers, primarily 1905-1935.
5 boxes
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collections was assembled from a variety of sources.
Periodic additions to the collection are expected.
The collection is open to research.
The Bentley Historical Library as a repository of Michigan-based materials has accumulated from different sources a collection of automobile catalogs. These catalogs are an important source for the study of the development of the automobile industry in Michigan.
The collection consists of trade catalogs, brochures and other promotional material produced by Michigan automobile manufacturers, primarily 1905-1935.The collection has been arranged alphabetically by name of automobile company. A few catalogs from non-Michigan companies are included, mainly Indiana, Ohio and New York companies.
Subjects:
Automobiles--Catalogs.; Aerocar Company of Detroit--Catalogs.; Alden Sampson Manufacturing Company--Catalogs.; Alpena Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; American Voiturette Company--Catalogs.; Anderson Electric Car Company--Catalogs.; Anhut Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; C.H. Blomstrom Motor Company--Catalogs.; Briggs-Detroiter Company--Catalogs.; Buick Motor Company--Catalogs.; Cadillac Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Chalmers-Detroit Motor Company--Catalogs.; Chevrolet Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Chrysler Corporation--Catalogs.; Church Manufacturing Company--Catalogs.; Cole Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Colonial Automobile Company--Catalogs.; Commerce Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Courier Car Company--Catalogs.; Day Automobile Company--Catalogs.; Demotcar Sales Company--Catalogs.; Detroit-Dearborn Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Dort Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Durant Motors, Inc.--Catalogs.; E-M-F Company--Catalogs.; Flint Motor Company--Catalogs.; Dodge Brothers--Catalogs.; Ford Motor Company--Catalogs.; H. H. Franklin Manufacturing Company--Catalogs.; General Motors Corporation--Catalogs.; General Motors Corporation. Buick Motor Division--Catalogs.; General Motors Corporation. Cadillac Motor Car Division--Catalogs.; General Motors Corporation. Chevrolet Motor Division--Catalogs.; General Motors Corporation. Oldsmobile Division--Catalogs.; General Motors Corporation. Pontiac Motor Division--Catalogs.; Graham-Paige Motors Corporation--Catalogs.; Harrison Wagon Company--Catalogs.; Herreshoff Motor Company--Catalogs.; Huber Automobile Company--Catalogs.; Hudson Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Hupp Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Jackson Automobile Company--Catalogs.; Johnson Service Company--Catalogs.; Kaiser Frazer Corp.--Catalogs.; King Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Kissel Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; K-R-I-T Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; LeBaron, Inc.--Catalogs.; Lewis Spring & Axle Company--Catalogs.; Lincoln Motor Company (Detroit, Mich.)--Catalogs.; Lion Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Metzger Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Michigan Automobile Company--Catalogs.; Michigan Motor Car Manufacturing Company--Catalogs.; Munson Company--Catalogs.; Nash Motors Company--Catalogs.; National Motor Vehicle Company--Catalogs.; Oakland Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Olds Motor Works--Catalogs.; Packard Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Paige-Detroit Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; W.A. Paterson Company--Catalogs.; Reo Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Saxon Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Springfield Body Company--Catalogs.; Studebaker Corporation--Catalogs.; E.R. Thomas Detroit Company--Catalogs.; Warren Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Welch Motor Car Company--Catalogs.; Willys-Overland Motors, Inc.--Catalogs.; Winton Motor Carriage Company--Catalogs.
Genre Terms:
Trade catalogs--Indiana--Indianapolis.; Trade catalogs--Indiana--La Porte.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Adrian.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Alpena.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Chelsea.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Dearborn.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Detroit.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Flint.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Grand Rapids.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Jackson.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Kalamazoo.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Lansing.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Pontiac.; Trade catalogs--Michigan--Willow Run.; Trade catalogs--New York (State)--New York.; Trade catalogs--New York (State)--Syracuse.; Trade catalogs--Ohio--Cleveland.; Trade catalogs--Ohio--Dayton.; Trade catalogs--Ohio--Toledo.; Trade catalogs--Wisconsin--Hartford.; Trade catalogs--Wisconsin--Kenosha.
- Aerocar - Flint Motors
  - Aerocar Company of Detroit, Detroit, Mich. (Box 1)
    - The Aerocar land yachts undated (Box 1)
      (folded leaflet illustrating trailers)
    - 9 pages of photographs of Aerocar trailers (Box 1)
  - Alden Sampson Mfg. Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - The Sampson thirty-five circa 1911 (Box 1)
  - Alpena Motor Car Co., Alpena, Mich.
    - Prospectus for preferred stock offering circa 1912 (Box 1)
  - American Voiturette Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - The triple test [pamphlet advertising the Keeton and Car-Nation cars] circa 1914 (Box 1)
  - Anderson Electric Car Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - The Detroit electric 1911 (Box 1)
  - Bi-Autogo (James Scripps Booth)
    - The Bi-Autogo, world's first large two-wheeled car 1908-1912, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Black Roadster, (no company given).
    - Black roadtser undated (Box 1)
  - Briggs-Detroiter Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Advertising brochure for the Detroiter Model D "Eight," 1915 (Box 1)
  - Buick Motor Car Co., Flint, Mich.
    - Buick 1910 specifications (Box 1)
    - Buick mechanical features models 16 and 17 1910 (Box 1)
    - 1912 Buick models 28-29 (Box 1)
    - 6 brilliant performers, Marquette, built by Buick 1930 (Box 1)
    - Buick for 1930 [booklet and advertising brochure] (Box 1)
    - Buick valve-in-head straight 8 1931 (Box 1)
    - Advertising brochure 1932 (Box 1)
    - New thousands can now own this big Buick straight eight sedan 1932 (Box 1)
    - Buick series 50 straight eight 1932 (Box 1)
    - Series 50 Buick straight eight for 1932 (Box 1)
    - Advertisement 1939 Buick Century (Box 1)
    - Buick 1940 (Box 1)
    - Two advertising brochures 1940 (Box 1)
    - Flint and the auto era 1945 (Box 1)
    - Two articles from GM Folks Magazine advertising new models 1938, 1951 (Box 1)
    - A quick look at Buick yesterday and today 1967 (Box 1)
    - For gallantry in action: The Buick Limited Undated (outsize) (Box 1)
    - The Buick eight for 1932 (outsize) (Box 1)
    - Buick 1940 (outsize) (Box 1)
  - The C.H. Blomstrom Motor Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Queen gasoline automobiles, runabouts & touring cars 1905 (Box 1)
  - Cadillac Motor Car Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Cadillac 1912 instructions for care and operation (Box 1)
    - Cadillac 1912 special instructions for starting engine (Box 1)
    - Cadillac 1912 advance leaflet (Box 1)
      (2 copies)
    - The story of the Cadillac Undated (Box 1)
    - The story of the Cadillac Undated 2 copies (Box 1)
    - The story of the Cadillac Undated (Box 1)
    - A new interpretation of motoring security Undated (Box 1)
    - New interpretations of motoring luxury Undated (Box 1)
    - Presenting the new LaSalle Town Sedan Undated (Box 1)
    - Three advertising brochures for the LaSalle undated (Box 1)
    - Eight miscellaneous advertising brochures and photographs (Box 1)
    - The Cadillac eight circa 1931 (Box 1)
    - Cadillac presents the new 1936 LaSalle (Box 1)
  - Chalmers-Detroit Motor Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - The champion car 1909 (Box 1)
    - The 1909 models (Box 1)
    - Chalmers-Detroit cars 1910 (Box 1)
      [includes 5 loose color plates]
    - Chalmers 1911 models, 3 copies (Box 1)
    - Advertisement for Chalmers-Detroit "30" limousine Undated (Box 1)
  - Chevrolet Motor Car Co. (and General Motors Corp. Chevrolet Divison), Detroit Mich.
    - The greatest Chevrolet in Chevrolet history 1930 (Box 1)
    - Three new Chevrolet models Undated (Box 1)
    - New Chevrolet six 1932 (Box 1)
    - Four advertising brochures 1939, 1940, 1941 (Folder NB D48 A938)
      (2 copies of 1941)
    - Advertising brochure 1964 (Box 1)
  - Chrysler Sales Corp., Detroit, Mich.
    - DeSoto announces new motor cars... Undated (Box 2)
    - DeSoto six Undated (Box 2)
    - El Chrysler "65" Undated (Box 2)
      (in Spanish)
    - The new DeSoto eight Undated (Box 2)
    - The Chrysler eight Undated (Box 2)
    - Chrysler Imperial eight Undated (Box 2)
    - Chrysler builds an eight with an all steel body Undated (Box 2)
    - The Chrysler eight Undated (Box 2)
    - The new Chrysler six Undated (Box 2)
    - The Chrysler Retailer v.l no.3 September 28, 1931 (Box 2)
    - A style that re-styles all motor cars Undated (Box 2)
    - Advertising brochure for the Chrysler "75," Undated (Box 2)
    - Six advertising pamphlets for the Chrysler Plymouth undated (Box 2)
    - Two advertisements for the Chrysler Plymouth 1939 (Box 2)
    - The Chrysler Magazine (name varies) 1941-1956, 8 issues scattered (Box 2)
    - The beautiful Chrysler 1940 (Box 2)
    - 1940 Plymouth Road King (Box 2)
    - DeLuxe Plymouth for 1940 (Box 2)
  - Church Manufacturing Co, .Adrian, Mich.
    - Photostats of 3 undated advertising pamphlets (Box 2)
  - Cole Motor Co., Indianapolis Ind.
    - Cole 30, a car with superb and ssilent service 1912 (Box 2)
    - Cole Wins, Henderson Bulletin September 16, 1911 (Box 2)
  - Colonial Automobile Co., Indianaplis, Ind.
    - The Colonial Six undated (Box 2)
  - Commerce Motor Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Detroit-Dearborn touring torpedo 1910 (Box 2)
  - Detroit-Dearborn Motor Co., Dearborn, Mich.
    - 1912 Commerce motor car (Box 2)
  - Dodge Brothers, Inc., Detroit, Mich. (Box 2)
    - DB [illustrated brochure] 1917 (Box 2)
    - Dodge Brothers motor cars 1925 (Box 2)
    - Dodge Brothers motor cars in special types 1925 (Box 2)
    - New Dodge six 1931 (Box 2)
    - New Dodge eight 1931 (Box 2)
    - New Dodge six Undated (Box 2)
    - New Dodge eight Undated (Box 2)
    - Dodge Brothers six Undated (Box 2)
    - A new six by Dodge Brothers Undated (Box 2)
    - New Dodge eight, brilliantly advanced-traditionally fine Undated (Box 2)
    - A new eight in line Undated (Box 2)
    - New Dodge six, a new pace-a new spirit Undated (Box 2)
    - New Dodge Brothers six Undated (Box 2)
    - A new eight in line by Dodge Brothers Undated (Box 2)
    - Standard-size [19]63 Dodge (Box 2)
    - 1963 compact Dodge Dart (Box 2)
    - Dodge News February 1940-September 1963 174 Dodge automobile advertisements clipped from issues of the Dodge News; some complete issues (Box 2)
    - 1940 Dodge Luxury Liner (Box 2)
  - Dort Motor Car Co.m Flint, Mich.
    - Dort Motor cars 1916 (Box 2)
  - Durant Motors, Inc., Flint, Mich.
    - Stock certificate 1924 (Box 2)
  - E-M-F Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - "The Hyphen" v.l no.1 Undated (Box 2)
    - Flanders 20 circa 1909 (Box 2)
    - A technical description, Flanders 20 1910 (Box 2)
    - E-M-F "30" 1910 touring car (Box 2)
  - Flint Motor Co., Flint, Mich.
    - The Flint six Undated (Box 2)
- Ford - Hupp
  - Ford Motor Co., Dearborn, Mich.
    - The Ford cars 1910, 2 copies (Box 3)
    - Ford motor cars 1910 (Box 3)
    - Ford town cars and coupes circa 1910 (Box 3)
    - Ford motor cars souvenir booklet 1910 (Box 3)
    - The fourth birthday party, telling when each Ford car...was born...by Murray Fahnestock (Box 3)
      (from Ford Owner and Dealer, June 1921)
    - The story of the new Ford car circa 1927 (Box 3)
    - The new Ford Victoria Undated (Box 3)
    - Ford Illustrated News Undated (Box 3)
    - The new Ford deluxe body types Undated (Box 3)
    - The new Ford, value far above the price 1931 (Box 3)
    - Ford V8 instruction book 1935 (Box 3)
    - Fifty years of Ford progress 1946 (Box 3)
    - Ford '55: The fine car of its field 1955 (Box 3)
    - Ford station wagons 1956 (Box 3)
    - Humorous post card, "Henry Ford has made walking popular" (Box 3)
    - Two advertisements for the Ford Tot-Guard child safety shield 1970-1971 (Box 3)
    - "Rough going on trans-Canada route in 1925" 1962 (Box 3)
      (appeared in the Dispatch, summer 1962 staff magazine of the Department of Public Works, Canada)
  - Fuller Buggy Company, Jackson, Mich.
    - Fuller automobiles, advance catalogue 1910 Automobile section in two parts (Box 3)
  - General Motors Corp., Detroit, Mich.
    - General
      - "Le Sabre is revealed", form G.M. Folks January 21, 1951 (Box 3)
      - The Automobile Buyer's Guide 1934 ed. [General Motors Customer Research staff] (Box 3)
      - Up from '29, 10 years of progress 1938 (Folder NB D48 A938)
        (shelved at NB D483 A938)
      - General Motors presents its 1941 model cars (Box 3)
      - General Motors builds its first 50 million cars 1954 (Box 3)
      - GM '58 (Box 3)
      - GM 1959 (Box 3)
      - For fun in '61 (Box 3)
      - Headed for a typical General Motors success... Undated (outsize) (Box 3)
  - Graham-Paige Motors Corp., Detroit, Mich.
    - As another year begins Undated (Box 3)
    - As another year begins Undated (Box 3)
    - Graham special six Undated (Box 3)
    - Graham eights Undated (Box 3)
    - Here it is! Blue Streak 1932 (Box 3)
    - The Graham eight twenty-two 1931 (Box 3)
    - A truly modern motor car Undated (Box 3)
    - Nine advertising brochures Undated (Box 3)
  - H.H. Franklin Manufacturing Co., Syracuse, N.Y.
    - Franklin Automobiles, simplicity vs. complexity circa 1910 (Box 3)
  - Harrison Motor Car Co., Grand Rapids, Mich. (Box 3)
    - The Harrison motor car, "The car without a crank," Model 13 circa 1906 (Box 3)
  - Herreshoff Motor Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Herreshoff "Winners by land and sea," 1912 (Box 3)
  - Huber Automobile Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - The Huber Automobile Company circa 1900s (Box 3)
  - Hudson Motor Car Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Hudson Six 54, the new ideal of a distinguished car undated (Box 3)
    - Hudson 1910, 2 copies (Box 3)
    - The Hudson six-fifty four Undated (Box 3)
    - The Hudson for 1911 (Box 3)
    - How to choose a motor car circa 1912 (Box 3)
    - Hudson cars for 1912 (Box 3)
    - Hudson motor cars for 1912, 2 copies (Box 3)
    - The Hudson "twenty" 1910 (Box 3)
    - The spirit of youth Undated (Box 3)
    - The Hudson light six-40 1915 (Box 3)
    - Hudson closed cars 1916 (Box 3)
    - The Greater Hudson Undated (Box 3)
    - The Greater Hudson 8 Undated (Box 3)
    - Hudson enclosed cars for 1915 (Box 3)
    - The Hudson Triangle v.7 no.23 December 1, 1917 (Box 3)
    - Hudson Motor Cars 1920 (Box 3)
    - The yacht-line Hudson six-40 Undated (Box 3)
    - The greater Hudson eight for 1931 (Box 3)
    - The new Hudson super-six pacemaker 1933 (Box 3)
    - Hudson pacemaker eight, major series 1933 (Box 3)
    - Hudson pacemaker eight, standard series 1933 (Box 3)
    - 1934 Hudson eight (Box 3)
    - The 1935 Hudson sixes and eights (Box 3)
    - Automotive Daily News January 13, 1934 Terraplane-Hudson section (Box 3)
    - The new Hudson sixes and eights 1936 (Box 3)
    - Hudson super-six. It solved motordom's knottiest problem Undated (Box 3)
    - Announcing new series Hudson super coaches Undated (Box 3)
    - Hudson "light six" motor car Undated (Box 3)
    - New 1942 Hudson (Box 3)
    - Hudson in the jubilee parade of progress 1946 (Box 3)
    - A sample convinces, demonstrations are samples, make more demonstrations [Manual for salesmen] Undated (Box 3)
    - Questions and answers for Hudson-Essex retail salesmen 1931 (Box 3)
      (2 parts)
    - The new Hudson convertible brougham 1948 (Box 3)
    - Advertising card 1949 (Box 3)
    - Hudson motor cars 1912 (Box 3)
      (outsize)
    - Hudson-Essex 1932 (Box 3)
    - Essex instruction book, Essex super six April 1930, photocopy (Box 3)
    - The new Essex super-six 1931 (Box 3)
    - Rare riding and driving comfort $595 Essex super-six Undated (Box 3)
    - Essex Terraplane circa 1932 (Box 3)
    - Terraplane 8 1933 (Box 3)
    - Terraplane 6 1933 (Box 3)
    - The Essex Terraplane special six Undated (Box 3)
    - The 1935 Hudson-built Terraplane (Box 3)
    - 1936 Terraplane (Box 3)
    - Terraplane 1936, 2 editions (Box 3)
    - Automotive Daily News November 26, 1930 (Folder NB D48 A938)
    - 1934 Hudson Terraplane, 2 oversize volumes (Box 3)
  - Hupp Motor Car Corp., Detroit, Mich.
    - Advertising brochure 1910 (Box 4)
    - Another year -- ans still no rival 1911 (Box 4)
    - The Hupmobile for 1916 (Box 4)
    - Advertising brochure 1916 (Box 4)
    - The new Hupmobile Century eight Undated (Box 4)
    - The new Hupmobile Century 6 Undated (Box 4)
    - Hupmobile series R 1921 (Box 4)
    - Hupmobile 1931 (Box 4)
    - The new Hupmobiles 1932 (Box 4)
    - Modern 1932 Hupmobiles (Box 4)
- Jackson Automobile Co. -- Olds Motor Works
  - Jackson Automobile Co., Jackson, Mich.
    - Jackson model "21" circa 1912 (Box 4)
    - Jackson model "30" circa 1912 (Box 4)
    - Jackson model "38" circa 1912 (Box 4)
    - Jackson model "41" circa 1912 (Box 4)
    - Jackson model "51" circa 1912 (Box 4)
    - Jackson Automobile Company circa 1906 (Box 4)
    - Details of construction 1913 (Box 4)
    - Jackson, no hill too steep, no sand to deep 1916, 2 copies (Box 4)
    - Advertisement circa 1917 (Box 4)
    - Dealer booklet 1918 (Box 4)
  - Johnson Service Co.
    - The auto-carriage circa 1901 (Box 4)
  - K-R-I-T Motor Car Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Cuts and specifications for KRIT automobiles 1910 (Box 4)
    - Krit motor cars 1912 (Box 4)
  - Kaiser Frazer Corp., Willow Run, Mich.
    - Kaiser-Frazer Dealer News, v.7 no.4 February 28, 1953 (Folder NB D48 A938)
      (shelved at NB 483 A938)
  - King Motor Car Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - King motor cars 1912 (Box 4)
    - Announcement, Model C Undated (Box 4)
    - Eight cylinder King 1915 (Box 4)
  - Kissel Motor Car Co., Hartford, Wis.
    - The custom built car Undated (Box 4)
  - Le Baron, Inc. (designers of car bodies), New York, N.Y. (Box 4)
    - Design book 1929-30 (Box 4)
    - Design book 1930-31 (Box 4)
  - Lewis Spring & Axle Co., Chelsea, Mich.
    - And now comes the 1917 Hollier six (Box 4)
    - Hollier eight, six, four 1917 (Box 4)
    - Introducing the 1917 Hollier eight (Box 4)
    - The Hollier eight, [undated] (Box 4)
    - [Album of images used in Hollier catalogs. undated.] (Box 4)
  - Lincoln Motor Company, Detroit, Mich.
    - Lincoln travelogue of art and transportation down through the ages 1926 (Box 4)
    - The Lincoln, a few distinguished body types Undated (Box 4)
    - A women looks at the Lincoln-Zephyr 1936 (Box 4)
    - Lincoln-Zephyr V-12 circa 1936 (Box 4)
  - Lion Motor Car Co., Adrian, Mich.
    - Series of 4 articles in the Adrian Telegram August 5-September 2, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Metzger Motor Car Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Everitt motor cars 1912 (Box 4)
    - Advance catalog 1912 Everitt (Box 4)
  - Michigan Automobile Co., Kalamazoo, Mich.
    - The Michigan automobile Undated (Box 4)
  - Michigan Motor Car Manufacturing Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Michigan "six" 1910 (Box 4)
  - The Munson Co., La Porte, Ind.
    - 1950 reprint of 1896 automobile catalog (Box 4)
  - Nash Motors Co., Kenosha, Wis.
    - Advertisement undated (Box 4)
    - Full speed ahead circa 1916 (Box 4)
    - Great cars for fifty years, golden anniversary. Nash Airflyte Magazine, v.3 no.5 1952 (Box 4)
  - Oakland Motor Car Co. and General Motors Corp. Pontiac Motor Division
    - New series Pontiac big six Undated (Box 4)
    - Oakland eight, the car with superior performance Undated (Box 4)
    - Oakland automobiles for 1910 (Box 4)
    - Oakland motor cars 1910 (Box 4)
    - The Oakland all-American six Undated (Box 4)
    - A new all-American six Undated (Box 4)
    - The new and finer Pontiac six Undated (Box 4)
    - The new Pontiac big six Undated (Box 4)
    - The new Pontiac big six Undated (Box 4)
    - Pontiac the fine 6 Undated (Box 4)
    - Pontiac V8 Undated (Box 4)
    - The sensational car in the low-priced field 1933 (Box 4)
    - Pontiac Chieftain 1937-1939, 3 issues (Box 4)
    - Pictures of Pontiac models 1934-1942 (Box 4)
  - E.R. Thomas Detroit Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Thomas-Detroti cars 1908 (Box 5)
  - Olds Motor Works (and General Motors Corp. Oldsmobile Division), Lansing, Mich.
    - 13 advertisements, 1902-03 (Box 5)
    - Oldsmobile special (1910) touring car (Box 5)
    - The Oldsmobile six 1930 (Box 5)
    - The Viking eight 1931 (Box 5)
    - The Oldsmobile six 1931 (Box 5)
    - 4 advertising brochures, 1930-32 (Box 5)
    - Oldsmobile [19]58 (Box 5)
    - Oldsmobile new six and eight Undated (outsize) (Box 5)
- Packard Motor Car Co.,- Winton Motor Co.
  - Packard Motor Car Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - 2 advertisements 1902-1903 (Box 5)
    - Packard motor cars 1911 (Box 5)
    - Attributes of Packard circa 1926 (Box 5)
    - The Packard eight circa 1928 (Box 5)
    - The Packard standard eight 1929 (Box 5)
    - Advertisement 1929 (Box 5)
    - The arts and crafts of Packard Undated (Box 5)
    - 1941 advertising brochure (Box 5)
    - Celebrating motordom's golden jubilee 1946 (Box 5)
    - A star is born, Packard Clipper 1941 (Box 5)
    - 4 advertising pictures Undated (Box 5)
    - 1938 Packard six owners manual (Box 5)
    - Packard custom cars Undated (outsize) (Box 5)
  - Paige-Detroit Motor Car Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Advance announcement 1912 models (Box 5)
    - Paige, the standard of value and quality 1915 (Box 5)
  - Parry Auto Company, Indianapolis, Ind
    - Parry cars for 1910 (Box 5)
  - Reo Motor Car Co., Lansing, Mich. (Box 5)
    - The mighty Reo for 1910 (Box 5)
    - Reo Undated (Box 5)
    - Invitation to preview showing Undated (Box 5)
    - Reo Flying Clouds Undated (Box 5)
    - The new Reo Flying Cloud eight Undated (Box 5)
    - The new Reo Flying Cloud six Undated (Box 5)
    - A new Reo-Royale eight Undated (Box 5)
    - 5 brochures for the Reo-Royale eight Undated (Box 5)
    - Reo Flying Cloud six Undated (Box 5)
    - Reo Flying Cloud eight Undated (Box 5)
    - The new Reo-Royale eight Undated (Box 5)
    - Reo closed cars circa 1923 (Box 5)
  - Saxon Motor Car Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Saxon days Undated (Box 5)
  - Springfield Body Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Springfield type bodies Undated (Box 5)
  - Studebaker Corp., Detroit, Mich.
    - Advertising brochure 1912 (Box 5)
    - Studebaker Flanders 20, preliminary catalog 1912 (Box 5)
    - The Studebaker automobile book circa 1914 (Box 5)
    - 10 clippings from The Studebaker News 1916-1917 (Box 5)
    - New 1949 Studebaker (Box 5)
  - W.A. Patterson Co., Flint, Mich.
    - 1910 Patterson "30" (Box 5)
    - Introducing 1913 line of Patterson cars (Box 5)
  - Warren Motor Car Co., Detroit, Mich.
    - Warren-Detroit "30," undated (Box 5)
    - Warren-Detroit "30," 1911 (Box 5)
  - Welch Motor Car Co., Pontiac, Mich.
    - Detail description of the Welch Motor Car Company's 1905 four-cylinder touring car (Box 5)
    - The book of Welch cars 1909 (Box 5)
    - The Welch motor car 1910 (Box 5)
    - "I just lost my head," article by Ralph Stein in Argosy December 1953, on the 1907 Welch (Box 5)
    - "I fell for America's craziest hobby," article by Ralph Stein in This Week Magazine September 13, 1953 on the 1907 Welch (Box 5)
    - 1 undated photograph (Box 5)
  - Willys-Overland Co., Toledo, Ohio
    - The Willys-Knight motor Undated (Box 5)
    - Specifications and features: the new Aero Willys Undated (Box 5)
    - The new Willys deluxe station Undated (Box 5)
    - Willys sedan delivery Undated (Box 5)
    - Special vehicles Undated (Box 5)
    - Don't handle with care Undated (Box 5)
    - Universal Jeep will do more jobs for you Undated (Box 5)